Tufts-New England Medical Center Records MS224
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
- Administration records, 1929 -- 1985; 1970 -- 1980; MS224.002; 20.4 Linear Feet
  - Educational Media Center - Financial, 1977; MS224.002.004.00005 (Box 4)
  - Educational Media Center - Financial, 1975 -- 1976; MS224.002.004.00006 (Box 4)
  - Educational Media Center - Financial, 1974 -- 1975; MS224.002.004.00007 (Box 4)
  - Educational Media Center budget proposal, 1975; MS224.002.004.00008 (Box 4)
  - Budget, 1974; MS224.002.004.00009 (Box 4)
  - Educational Media Center - Financial, 1973 -- 1974; MS224.002.004.00010 (Box 4)
  - Suspense: Mary Brown, 1971 -- 1973; MS224.002.004.00011 (Box 4)
  - Learning Resource Committee, 1977; MS224.002.004.00012 (Box 4)
  - Position Questionaire, 1977; MS224.002.004.00013 (Box 4)
  - Educational Media Center special committee, 1971 -- 1972; MS224.002.004.00014 (Box 4)
  - Educational Media Center review committee, 1974; MS224.002.004.00015 (Box 4)
  - August 18th, MS224.002.004.00016 (Box 4)
    Folder is empty.
  - July 14th, MS224.002.004.00017 (Box 4)
  - July 15th, MS224.002.004.00018 (Box 4)
  - July 16th, MS224.002.004.00019 (Box 4)
  - July 17th, MS224.002.004.00020 (Box 4)
  - July 18th, MS224.002.004.00021 (Box 4)
  - Educational Media Center Budget Review, 1972; MS224.002.004.00022 (Box 4)
  - Educational Media Center budget, 1971 -- 1972; MS224.002.004.00023 (Box 4)
  - Educational Media Center budget, 1970 -- 1971; MS224.002.004.00024 (Box 4)
  - General, 1970 -- 1973; MS224.002.004.00025 (Box 4)
  - Educational Media Center, 1972 -- 1973; MS224.002.004.00026 (Box 4)
  - Parking Rates, 1975 -- 1977; MS224.002.004.00027 (Box 4)
  - Properties Financial, 1975 -- 1976; MS224.002.004.00028 (Box 4)
  - Parking Observation, 1976; MS224.002.004.00029 (Box 4)
  - Parking Memos, 1977; MS224.002.004.00030 (Box 4)
  - Garage Lighting Survey, 1974 -- 1975; MS224.002.004.00031 (Box 4)
  - 723 Listing, 1975 -- 1976; MS224.002.004.00032 (Box 4)
  - System Employee, 1975 -- 1976; MS224.002.004.00033 (Box 4)
  - System Auto Park, 1974 -- 1977; MS224.002.004.00034 (Box 4)
  - Garage Survey, 1974; MS224.002.004.00035 (Box 4)
  - Garage - Bradford parking, 1974; MS224.002.004.00036 (Box 4)
  - Parking Guide, MS224.002.004.00037 (Box 4)
  - Bill sent to California for payment, 1976; MS224.002.004.00038 (Box 4)
  - Bill sent to California for payment, 1976; MS224.002.004.00039 (Box 4)
  - Bill sent to California for payment, 1976; MS224.002.004.00040 (Box 4)
  - Bill sent to California for payment, 1976; MS224.002.004.00041 (Box 4)
  - Bill sent to California for payment, 1976; MS224.002.004.00042 (Box 4)
  - Bill sent to California for payment, 1976; MS224.002.004.00043 (Box 4)
  - Bill sent to California for payment, 1976; MS224.002.004.00044 (Box 4)
  - Educational Media Center resumes, 1971 -- 1972; MS224.002.004.00045 (Box 4)
  - Systems Computer Printout Monthly Expenses, 1975 -- 1976; MS224.002.004.00046 (Box 4)
  - Educational Media Center P.A.C., 1971; MS224.002.004.00047 (Box 4)
  - Garage Security, 1974 -- 1977; MS224.002.004.00048 (Box 4)
  - Parking Liability, 1976; MS224.002.004.00049 (Box 4)
  - Parking Guide, 1975 -- 1977; MS224.002.004.00050 (Box 4)
  - Delinquent Parking, 1974 -- 1976; MS224.002.004.00051 (Box 4)
  - NEPA, 1977; MS224.002.004.00052 (Box 4)
  - Garage Elevators - Westing House Haugton, 1973 -- 1976; MS224.002.004.00053 (Box 4)
  - Garage Edison Bills, 1974 -- 1977; MS224.002.004.00054 (Box 4)
  - Parking Excise Tax, 1977 -- 1978; MS224.002.004.00055 (Box 4)
  - Reduced Parking Rate for Long Term P/V, 1975 -- 1977; MS224.002.004.00056 (Box 4)
  - Garage - Capital Improvements, 1976 -- 1977; MS224.002.004.00057 (Box 4)
  - Bill sent to California for payment, 1975; MS224.002.004.00058 (Box 4)
  - Bill sent to California for payment, 1976; MS224.002.004.00059 (Box 4)
  - Bill sent to California for payment, 1976; MS224.002.004.00060 (Box 4)
  - Bill sent to California for payment, 1976; MS224.002.005.00001 (Box 5)
  - Bill sent to California for payment, 1976; MS224.002.005.00002 (Box 5)
  - Bill sent to California for payment, 1976; MS224.002.005.00003 (Box 5)
  - Bill sent to California for payment, 1975; MS224.002.005.00004 (Box 5)
  - Bill sent to California for payment, 1975; MS224.002.005.00005 (Box 5)
  - Bill sent to California for payment, 1975; MS224.002.005.00006 (Box 5)
  - Bill sent to California for payment, 1975; MS224.002.005.00007 (Box 5)
  - Bill sent to California for payment, 1975; MS224.002.005.00008 (Box 5)
  - MBTA Garage, 1971 -- 1975; MS224.002.005.00009 (Box 5)
  - New Parking Garage Contracts, 1971; MS224.002.005.00010 (Box 5)
  - Garage - EEO, 1971 -- 1972; MS224.002.005.00011 (Box 5)
  - New Parking Garage Reports, 1971; MS224.002.005.00012 (Box 5)
  - Parking Garage - Bridge, 1971 -- 1973; MS224.002.005.00013 (Box 5)
  - Garage Outline Specifications, 1971; MS224.002.005.00014 (Box 5)
  - Garage Rental, 1971 -- 1973; MS224.002.005.00015 (Box 5)
  - Garage Mortgage, 1971 -- 1973; MS224.002.005.00016 (Box 5)
  - Garage Taxes, 1971 -- 1973; MS224.002.005.00017 (Box 5)
  - New Parking Garage Financing, 1971; MS224.002.005.00018 (Box 5)
  - Sprinklers, 1973; MS224.002.005.00019 (Box 5)
  - T-NEMC Charges for Parking Garage, 1972 -- 1973; MS224.002.005.00020 (Box 5)
  - Signs, 1972 -- 1974; MS224.002.005.00021 (Box 5)
  - Garage Landscaping, 1973; MS224.002.005.00022 (Box 5)
  - Parking Garage - Construction, 1971 -- 1973; MS224.002.005.00023 (Box 5)
  - Parking: T-NEMC Eliot Street Garage, 1971 -- 1976; MS224.002.005.00024 (Box 5)
  - T-NEMC Eliot Street Garage, 1976; MS224.002.005.00025 (Box 5)
  - Security Force, 1972 -- 1974; MS224.002.005.00026 (Box 5)
  - Bicycles, 1970 -- 1972; MS224.002.005.00027 (Box 5)
  - Parking Complaints, 1969 -- 1975; MS224.002.005.00028 (Box 5)
  - Parking: General, 1967 -- 1974; MS224.002.005.00029 (Box 5)
  - Parking: Maps, 1972; MS224.002.005.00030 (Box 5)
  - Parking: Insurance, 1972; MS224.002.005.00031 (Box 5)
  - Parking: Real Estate, 1975; MS224.002.005.00032 (Box 5)
  - Parking: Bulletin, 1969 -- 1971; MS224.002.005.00033 (Box 5)
  - Parking: Operation, 1976; MS224.002.005.00034 (Box 5)
  - Parking: Personnel, 1970 -- 1972; MS224.002.005.00035 (Box 5)
  - Secretary's Manual re: Parking, MS224.002.005.00036 (Box 5)
  - Parking: Supplementary Records, 1973 -- 1974; MS224.002.005.00037 (Box 5)
  - Parking: Supplementary Records - Current, 1970; MS224.002.005.00038 (Box 5)
  - Parking: Supplementary Records - Unpaid Bills, 1970; MS224.002.005.00039 (Box 5)
  - Carpool Program, 1975; MS224.002.005.00040 (Box 5)
  - Parking Survey - Dental Students, MS224.002.005.00041 (Box 5)
  - Parking: Survey, 1971; MS224.002.005.00042 (Box 5)
  - Parking: Performance, 1970 -- 1974; MS224.002.005.00043 (Box 5)
  - Parking: Meyers Brothers, 1972 -- 1974; MS224.002.005.00044 (Box 5)
  - Parking: Meyers Brothers Contract, 1969 -- 1970; MS224.002.005.00045 (Box 5)
  - Parking: Miscellaneous, 1969 -- 1970; MS224.002.005.00046 (Box 5)
  - Parking: T-NEMC, 1969; MS224.002.005.00047 (Box 5)
  - Parking: Financial, 1969 -- 1970; MS224.002.005.00048 (Box 5)
  - System General, 1969 -- 1976; MS224.002.005.00049 (Box 5)
  - Parking Crowton, 1970; MS224.002.005.00050 (Box 5)
  - July Analysis, MS224.002.005.00051 (Box 5)
  - Parking: Assignment, current problems, 1969 -- 1970; MS224.002.005.00052 (Box 5)
  - Taxes, 1970 -- 1975; MS224.002.005.00053 (Box 5)
  - Metro taxes, 1969; MS224.002.005.00054 (Box 5)
  - Student Committee, 1970; MS224.002.005.00055 (Box 5)
  - Shopper's Garage, 1970; MS224.002.005.00056 (Box 5)
  - Parking: Rate study, 1972; MS224.002.005.00057 (Box 5)
  - Parking: Planning, 1969; MS224.002.005.00058 (Box 5)
  - Parking: Space available, 1971; MS224.002.005.00059 (Box 5)
  - Parking: Petition, MS224.002.005.00060 (Box 5)
  - Parking: Lot #721, 1970; MS224.002.005.00061 (Box 5)
  - Parking: Lot #722, 1970 -- 1971; MS224.002.005.00062 (Box 5)
  - Parking: Lot #720, 1970 -- 1971; MS224.002.005.00063 (Box 5)
  - Parking: Lot #719, 1971; MS224.002.005.00064 (Box 5)
  - Parking: Lot #713, 1972; MS224.002.005.00065 (Box 5)
  - Parking: Lot #714, 1969 -- 1971; MS224.002.005.00066 (Box 5)
  - Parking: Lot #701, 1970; MS224.002.005.00067 (Box 5)
  - B.R.A. Garage, MS224.002.005.00068 (Box 5)
  - Garage Maintenance - Repairs, MS224.002.005.00069 (Box 5)
  - Minority Employment, 1969 -- 1973; MS224.002.006.00001 (Box 6)
  - Minority Contracts, 1970 -- 1973; MS224.002.006.00002 (Box 6)
  - Boston Plans, 1970 -- 1971; MS224.002.006.00003 (Box 6)
  - EEO Clauses, 1970; MS224.002.006.00004 (Box 6)
  - Old EEO Clauses, 1969 -- 1970; MS224.002.006.00005 (Box 6)
  - EEO Statement of Position, 1970; MS224.002.006.00006 (Box 6)
  - EEO Job Description, 1970; MS224.002.006.00007 (Box 6)
  - EEO Counter Parts/Employment, 1970; MS224.002.006.00008 (Box 6)
  - EEO Construction, 1970; MS224.002.006.00009 (Box 6)
  - EEO - Medford Sources, 1970 -- 1971; MS224.002.006.00010 (Box 6)
  - EEO Procedures, 1970; MS224.002.006.00011 (Box 6)
  - Alien Employment, 1971; MS224.002.006.00012 (Box 6)
  - Sprague Associates, 1969 -- 1972; MS224.002.006.00013 (Box 6)
  - Sprague Medical Systems, 1969 -- 1970; MS224.002.006.00014 (Box 6)
  - Parking: Chinese Parking, 1970; MS224.002.006.00015 (Box 6)
  - Parking, 1951 -- 1956; MS224.002.006.00016 (Box 6)
  - Parking equipment - simplex, 1971 -- 1973; MS224.002.006.00017 (Box 6)
  - CVC parking, 1971; MS224.002.006.00018 (Box 6)
  - Parking: new parking garage, 1971 -- 1974; MS224.002.006.00019 (Box 6)
  - Chinese American Civic Association, 1973; MS224.002.006.00020 (Box 6)
  - Chinese Community: General, 1971; MS224.002.006.00021 (Box 6)
  - Correspondence - New Parking Project, 1969 -- 1971; MS224.002.006.00022 (Box 6)
  - New parking project, 1970; MS224.002.006.00023 (Box 6)
  - HEW Adult John Bynde, 1969 -- 1971; MS224.002.006.00024 (Box 6)
  - Incoming, 1970; MS224.002.006.00025 (Box 6)
  - Chinese Applications, 1971; MS224.002.006.00026 (Box 6)
    75 years from the date of creation.
  - Tufts-NEMC Garage (Sprague Industries), 1971; MS224.002.006.00027 (Box 6)
  - Additional Copy of Chinese Applications, 1971; MS224.002.006.00028 (Box 6)
  - Chinese Applications, 1971; MS224.002.006.00029 (Box 6)
  - Construction meeting agendas and minutes, 1970 -- 1972; MS224.002.006.00030 (Box 6)
  - Sprague Daily Averages, 1971; MS224.002.006.00031 (Box 6)
  - Boston Plan, 1970; MS224.002.006.00032 (Box 6)
  - Farina, 1970 -- 1971; MS224.002.006.00033 (Box 6)
  - Write-ups from Engineering, 1970; MS224.002.006.00034 (Box 6)
  - EEO Cost Control Unit-1A, 1971; MS224.002.006.00035 (Box 6)
  - Resumes and financial statements of minority contractors, 1971; MS224.002.006.00036 (Box 6)
  - Paint company (Afro students), 1971; MS224.002.006.00037 (Box 6)
  - Bids, 1967 -- 1970; MS224.002.007.00001 (Box 7)
  - Invitation to bid (Bidders), 1971; MS224.002.007.00002 (Box 7)
  - EEO-CC, 1972; MS224.002.007.00003 (Box 7)
  - Chinese Training Program, MS224.002.007.00004 (Box 7)
  - Plumber training, 1971; MS224.002.007.00005 (Box 7)
  - Status Report, 1970 -- 1971; MS224.002.007.00006 (Box 7)
  - Reports to Ed Ehrlich, 1971; MS224.002.007.00007 (Box 7)
  - Conferences EEO, 1973; MS224.002.007.00008 (Box 7)
  - The Boston Plan for Minority Group Employment in the Construction Industry, 1970; MS224.002.007.00009 (Box 7)
  - Garage Affirmative Action, 1971; MS224.002.007.00010 (Box 7)
  - Apprenticeship Program RTP, 1973; MS224.002.007.00011 (Box 7)
  - Available Positions, 1973; MS224.002.007.00012 (Box 7)
  - Correspondence - Education, 1973; MS224.002.007.00013 (Box 7)
  - Employment Discrimination T-NEMC, 1972; MS224.002.007.00014 (Box 7)
  - Legal Matters - EEO, MS224.002.007.00015 (Box 7)
  - Minority Workers List, MS224.002.007.00016 (Box 7)
  - Training Program - GED, MS224.002.007.00017 (Box 7)
  - Union Hospital Workers, 1973; MS224.002.007.00018 (Box 7)
  - Painting Contracts, 1973; MS224.002.007.00019 (Box 7)
  - Semi-Monthly Employment, 1972 -- 1973; MS224.002.007.00020 (Box 7)
  - Bids for Blood Bank, 1973; MS224.002.007.00021 (Box 7)
  - Sprague Daily Reports, 1972; MS224.002.007.00022 (Box 7)
  - Sprague Daily Reports, 1972; MS224.002.007.00023 (Box 7)
  - Sprague Daily Reports, 1972; MS224.002.007.00024 (Box 7)
  - Sprague Daily Reports, 1972; MS224.002.007.00025 (Box 7)
  - Sprague Daily Reports, 1973; MS224.002.007.00026 (Box 7)
  - Sprague Daily Reports, 1973; MS224.002.007.00027 (Box 7)
  - Workers defense league, 1972; MS224.002.007.00028 (Box 7)
  - Plumbers, 1971 -- 1972; MS224.002.007.00029 (Box 7)
  - Chinese, 1972; MS224.002.007.00030 (Box 7)
  - Incoming, 1972; MS224.002.007.00031 (Box 7)
  - Tufts University phase II, 1970 -- 1971; MS224.002.007.00032 (Box 7)
  - Mailing Lists, 1972; MS224.002.007.00033 (Box 7)
  - Outgoing, 1972; MS224.002.007.00034 (Box 7)
  - Letter to David Everhart, 1971; MS224.002.007.00035 (Box 7)
  - Minority vendors workshop, 1972; MS224.002.007.00036 (Box 7)
  - Reliance Electric Company Haughton Elevator Division EEO, 1970 -- 1971; MS224.002.007.00037 (Box 7)
  - New Boston plan, 1971; MS224.002.007.00038 (Box 7)
  - Barr & Barr daily reports, 1972; MS224.002.007.00039 (Box 7)
  - Barr & Barr daily reports, 1972; MS224.002.007.00040 (Box 7)
  - Barr & Barr daily reports, 1972; MS224.002.007.00041 (Box 7)
  - Barr & Barr daily reports, 1972; MS224.002.007.00042 (Box 7)
  - Barr & Barr daily reports, 1973; MS224.002.007.00043 (Box 7)
  - Barr & Barr daily reports, 1973; MS224.002.007.00044 (Box 7)
  - Barr & Barr daily reports, 1973; MS224.002.007.00045 (Box 7)
  - Semi-monthly Sprague, 1972; MS224.002.007.00046 (Box 7)
  - Incoming, 1970; MS224.002.007.00047 (Box 7)
  - Originals for Boston and Beyond, 1976; MS224.002.007.00048 (Box 7)
  - Helicopters, 1969 -- 1977; MS224.002.007.00049 (Box 7)
  - Medical Illustration Advisory Committee, 1967 -- 1969; MS224.002.007.00050 (Box 7)
  - Wentworth Institute, 1970; MS224.002.007.00051 (Box 7)
  - Spiker, Ellwyn, 1966 -- 1968; MS224.002.007.00052 (Box 7)
  - Parking correspondence, 1977 -- 1979; MS224.002.007.00053 (Box 7)
  - Parking correspondence, 1969 -- 1976; MS224.002.007.00054 (Box 7)
  - Lists, 1966 -- 1975; MS224.002.007.00055 (Box 7)
  - Parking Lot #711, 1972; MS224.002.007.00056 (Box 7)
  - Parking Lot #715, 1972; MS224.002.007.00057 (Box 7)
  - Parking Lot #716, 1968 -- 1973; MS224.002.007.00058 (Box 7)
  - Parking Lot #717, 1974; MS224.002.007.00059 (Box 7)
  - Parking Lot #718, 1970 -- 1977; MS224.002.007.00060 (Box 7)
  - Parking Lot #723, 1970 -- 1974; MS224.002.007.00061 (Box 7)
  - Eliot Street Garage, 1976 -- 1980; MS224.002.007.00062 (Box 7)
  - Rates, 1970 -- 1974; MS224.002.007.00063 (Box 7)
  - Parking: Systems' Contract, 1969 -- 1974; MS224.002.007.00064 (Box 7)
  - Herald Street Garage (Druker), MS224.002.007.00065 (Box 7)
  - Parking: historical information, 1968 -- 1969; MS224.002.007.00066 (Box 7)
  - New Parking Rates, 1970 -- 1975; MS224.002.007.00067 (Box 7)
  - Parking Operation, 1974 -- 1977; MS224.002.007.00068 (Box 7)
  - Statistics, 1974 -- 1977; MS224.002.007.00069 (Box 7)
  - Garage Insurance, 1972 -- 1974; MS224.002.008.00001 (Box 8)
  - Garage: Washington street median opening, 1971 -- 1973; MS224.002.008.00002 (Box 8)
  - Garage Security, 1973; MS224.002.008.00003 (Box 8)
  - Garage Plaza, 1973; MS224.002.008.00004 (Box 8)
  - Beef and Ale, 1971 -- 1977; MS224.002.008.00005 (Box 8)
  - Beef and Ale Lease, 1972 -- 1973; MS224.002.008.00006 (Box 8)
  - Garage Documents, 1972 -- 1977; MS224.002.008.00007 (Box 8)
  - Dr. Millis Financial, 1971 -- 1972; MS224.002.008.00008 (Box 8)
  - Millis, John, 1970 -- 1973; MS224.002.008.00009 (Box 8)
  - Project Coordinator Job Description, 1971; MS224.002.008.00010 (Box 8)
  - EEODO, 1972 -- 1973; MS224.002.008.00011 (Box 8)
  - T-NEMC Advisory Committee - EEO, 1970; MS224.002.008.00012 (Box 8)
  - EEO Clauses - General, 1970; MS224.002.008.00013 (Box 8)
  - Personnel Opportunity and Purchasing Committee - EEO, 1970; MS224.002.008.00014 (Box 8)
  - Equal Employment Opportunity Development Officer, 1970; MS224.002.008.00015 (Box 8)
  - Massachusetts Commission Against Discrimination, 1972 -- 1974; MS224.002.008.00016 (Box 8)
  - Executive order 11246, 1968 -- 1972; MS224.002.008.00017 (Box 8)
  - Course for Minority Contractors, 1971 -- 1972; MS224.002.008.00018 (Box 8)
  - Suspense - S. Scott, 1972; MS224.002.008.00019 (Box 8)
  - Alterations, 1969 -- 1972; MS224.002.008.00020 (Box 8)
  - Long range Planning - General, 1971 -- 1972; MS224.002.008.00021 (Box 8)
  - Planning Office - Library, 1969; MS224.002.008.00022 (Box 8)
  - Long range Planning - Budget, 1970 -- 1971; MS224.002.008.00023 (Box 8)
  - Allright Auto Parks, Inc., 1970 -- 1971; MS224.002.008.00024 (Box 8)
  - Garage - Equipment, 1972 -- 1973; MS224.002.008.00025 (Box 8)
  - Parking: Barton-Aschman, 1970; MS224.002.008.00026 (Box 8)
  - Parking: Consultants, 1974; MS224.002.008.00027 (Box 8)
  - Parking Lifts, 1971; MS224.002.008.00028 (Box 8)
  - Garage Operators, 1971 -- 1973; MS224.002.008.00029 (Box 8)
  - Park Garage, 1971 -- 1972; MS224.002.008.00030 (Box 8)
  - Dental Building - First National Bank, 1971 -- 1974; MS224.002.008.00031 (Box 8)
  - Dental Building - Bank Signs, 1973; MS224.002.008.00032 (Box 8)
  - Dental Building, 1970 -- 1974; MS224.002.008.00033 (Box 8)
  - T-NEMC Fund Raising Committee, 1967 -- 1971; MS224.002.008.00034 (Box 8)
  - Bradford Hotel, 1965 -- 1968; MS224.002.008.00035 (Box 8)
  - Bradford Hotel, 1957; MS224.002.008.00036 (Box 8)
  - Tufts Renovations, 1970; MS224.002.008.00037 (Box 8)
  - Dental Curriculum Administrative Committee, 1969; MS224.002.008.00038 (Box 8)
  - Procedures, 1970; MS224.002.008.00039 (Box 8)
  - Parking: User Comments, 1976 -- 1980; MS224.002.009.00001 (Box 9)
  - Parking: Control Equipment, 1976; MS224.002.009.00002 (Box 9)
  - Parking: Carpool, 1975; MS224.002.009.00003 (Box 9)
  - Bills sent to California for payment, 1980; MS224.002.009.00004 (Box 9)
  - Bills sent to California for payment, 1980; MS224.002.009.00005 (Box 9)
  - Bills sent to California for payment, 1980; MS224.002.009.00006 (Box 9)
  - Bills sent to California for payment, 1980; MS224.002.009.00007 (Box 9)
  - Bills sent to California for payment, 1980; MS224.002.009.00008 (Box 9)
  - Bills sent to California for payment, 1980; MS224.002.009.00009 (Box 9)
  - Bills sent to California for payment, 1979; MS224.002.009.00010 (Box 9)
  - Bills sent to California for payment, 1979; MS224.002.009.00011 (Box 9)
  - Bills sent to California for payment, 1979; MS224.002.009.00012 (Box 9)
  - Bills sent to California for payment, 1979; MS224.002.009.00013 (Box 9)
  - Bills sent to California for payment, 1979; MS224.002.009.00014 (Box 9)
  - Bills sent to California for payment, 1979; MS224.002.009.00015 (Box 9)
  - Bills sent to California for payment, 1979; MS224.002.009.00016 (Box 9)
  - Bills sent to California for payment, 1979; MS224.002.009.00017 (Box 9)
  - Bills sent to California for payment, 1979; MS224.002.009.00018 (Box 9)
  - Bills sent to California for payment, 1979; MS224.002.009.00019 (Box 9)
  - Bills sent to California for payment, 1979; MS224.002.009.00020 (Box 9)
  - Bills sent to California for payment, 1979; MS224.002.009.00021 (Box 9)
  - Bills sent to California for payment, 1978; MS224.002.009.00022 (Box 9)
  - Bills sent to California for payment, 1978; MS224.002.009.00023 (Box 9)
  - Bills sent to California for payment, 1978; MS224.002.009.00024 (Box 9)
  - Bills sent to California for payment, 1978; MS224.002.009.00025 (Box 9)
  - Bills sent to California for payment, 1978; MS224.002.009.00026 (Box 9)
  - Bills sent to California for payment, 1978; MS224.002.009.00027 (Box 9)
  - Bills sent to California for payment, 1978; MS224.002.009.00028 (Box 9)
  - Bills sent to California for payment, 1978; MS224.002.009.00029 (Box 9)
  - Bills sent to California for payment, 1978; MS224.002.009.00030 (Box 9)
  - Bills sent to California for payment, 1978; MS224.002.009.00031 (Box 9)
  - Parking: System, 1978 -- 1979; MS224.002.009.00032 (Box 9)
  - Parking: General, 1978 -- 1979; MS224.002.009.00033 (Box 9)
  - Parking: Budget Fiscal Year, 1974 -- 1975; MS224.002.009.00034 (Box 9)
  - Parking: Budget Fiscal Year, 1975 -- 1976; MS224.002.009.00035 (Box 9)
  - PROP. MBTA Orange Line, 1977 -- 1978; MS224.002.009.00036 (Box 9)
  - PROP. Nordblom, 1972 -- 1977; MS224.002.009.00037 (Box 9)
  - Plan IB air rights, 1974 -- 1977; MS224.002.009.00038 (Box 9)
  - Nordblom statements, 1976 -- 1977; MS224.002.009.00039 (Box 9)
  - Plan Chinatown News, 1975; MS224.002.009.00040 (Box 9)
  - PROP. Rent Control Board, 1976 -- 1977; MS224.002.010.00001 (Box 10)
  - Rehabilitation Engineering, 1979 -- 1980; MS224.002.010.00002 (Box 10)
  - Other T-NEMC General, 1975 -- 1980; MS224.002.010.00003 (Box 10)
  - PROP. Exterior Signage, 1972 -- 1978; MS224.002.010.00004 (Box 10)
  - PROP. Budget, 1977 -- 1978; MS224.002.010.00005 (Box 10)
  - USC - Monthly Reports and Budget Sheets, 1975 -- 1978; MS224.002.010.00006 (Box 10)
  - USC - General, 1975; MS224.002.010.00007 (Box 10)
  - Medical Engineering: General, 1977 -- 1980; MS224.002.010.00008 (Box 10)
  - Dental Building - Commercial Space, 1971 -- 1972; MS224.002.010.00009 (Box 10)
  - New Boston Bank, 1969 -- 1971; MS224.002.010.00010 (Box 10)
  - New England Merchants Bank, 1971 -- 1972; MS224.002.010.00011 (Box 10)
  - Medical Electronics Department, 1972 -- 1975; MS224.002.010.00012 (Box 10)
  - Building 1-A, 1970 -- 1974; MS224.002.010.00013 (Box 10)
  - 1B Conference Room, 1974 -- 1976; MS224.002.010.00014 (Box 10)
  - Hospital 1B, 1970 -- 1972; MS224.002.010.00015 (Box 10)
  - Library - Education Building, 1972; MS224.002.010.00016 (Box 10)
  - TAC General, 1969 -- 1975; MS224.002.010.00017 (Box 10)
  - TAC - History/Selection, 1964 -- 1972; MS224.002.010.00018 (Box 10)
  - Utility Plant Engineer, MS224.002.010.00019 (Box 10)
  - B.D. Emergency Generator, 1971; MS224.002.010.00020 (Box 10)
  - Construction Strike, 1971; MS224.002.010.00021 (Box 10)
  - Construction Art, 1970; MS224.002.010.00022 (Box 10)
  - Tufts Data, 1970; MS224.002.010.00023 (Box 10)
  - Developers, 1969 -- 1970; MS224.002.010.00024 (Box 10)
  - Construction - General, 1970 -- 1972; MS224.002.010.00025 (Box 10)
  - Pulmonary Functions Laboratory, 1973; MS224.002.010.00026 (Box 10)
  - Industrial Engineer, 1970; MS224.002.010.00027 (Box 10)
  - Central Utility, 1969 -- 1970; MS224.002.010.00028 (Box 10)
  - Balco Contract, 1972 -- 1974; MS224.002.010.00029 (Box 10)
  - Indemnific ation, 1970 -- 1972; MS224.002.010.00030 (Box 10)
  - Insurance, 1969 -- 1971; MS224.002.010.00031 (Box 10)
  - Construction - MBTA, 1970 -- 1971; MS224.002.010.00032 (Box 10)
  - Site Visit, 1969; MS224.002.010.00033 (Box 10)
  - Arnold Building - Parland Properties, 1971; MS224.002.010.00034 (Box 10)
  - Property Available, 1970 -- 1974; MS224.002.010.00035 (Box 10)
  - 37 Bennet Street, 1970 -- 1975; MS224.002.010.00036 (Box 10)
  - Bradford Hotel, 1969 -- 1972; MS224.002.010.00037 (Box 10)
  - Properties: Budget, 1970; MS224.002.010.00038 (Box 10)
  - Coffee Shop, 1970; MS224.002.010.00039 (Box 10)
  - Property Cost, 1959; MS224.002.010.00040 (Box 10)
  - Fuller building, 1972; MS224.002.010.00041 (Box 10)
  - Garage Space, 1973; MS224.002.010.00042 (Box 10)
  - Properties - General, 1970 -- 1977; MS224.002.010.00043 (Box 10)
  - Property - 17 Nassau Street, 1971 -- 1977; MS224.002.010.00044 (Box 10)
  - Metropolitan Building, 1961 -- 1974; MS224.002.010.00045 (Box 10)
  - Nordblom, 1971 -- 1973; MS224.002.010.00046 (Box 10)
  - 31 Oak Street, 1971 -- 1973; MS224.002.010.00047 (Box 10)
  - 31 Oak Street, 1969 -- 1972; MS224.002.010.00048 (Box 10)
  - Office Space, 1969 -- 1975; MS224.002.010.00049 (Box 10)
  - Property - Parcel C-1, MS224.002.010.00050 (Box 10)